# **PRINCESS TONAYON**

61 Ileayo Akesan Igando Lagos Nigeria (+234) 0816 750 9299

princessonome2017@gmail.com

## **OBJECTIVE**

A front-end web developer with 2years experience in creating user interface website for desktop and mobile use. My vision is to help businesses build custom website that will have significant effect on the growth of their business.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### 2019-2020

#### Front end developer (Freelancer)

I worked as a freelancer online as a front-end developer. I was rendering alot of services such as product landing page design, full page website, etc. I worked with HTML, CSS and Javascript Languages.

#### 2020-2021

## Front-end Developer & Technical Support Team

I worked as a front-end developer and also a technical support lead team at Flyte Technology and Solution Ltd. I was building user-interface design for software and web applications. Also I was involved in supporting clients with troubleshooting issues.

#### **EDUCATION**

National Diploma Lagos State Polytechnic 2017-2020 Computer Science

## **SKILLS**

## **Programming Language**

JAVASCRIPT

- HTML
- CSS

## **FRAMEWORK**

- BOOTSTRAP
- JQUERY

# **SOCIAL LINKS**

Portfolio Website: <a href="https://www.github.com/princess-ctrl.github.io/portfolio">https://www.github.com/princess-ctrl.github.io/portfolio</a>

**Github:** <a href="https://www.github.com/princess-ctrl">https://www.github.com/princess-ctrl</a>

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/princess-tonayon-0a904219a

Twitter: <a href="https://www.twitter.com/@TonayonPrincess">https://www.twitter.com/@TonayonPrincess</a>

## **LANGUAGES**

**ENGLISH** 

## **INTEREST**

Women Who Code (WWW) Artificial Intelligence Advocate

# Reference

Available on Request